起床了 Baltimore 现在是早上六点...
Wake up, Baltimore. It's 6:00 a.m....
警察
Police!
准备好了?
Ready?
不许动 FBI
Freeze, FBl!
- 安全 - 看看楼上
-All clear. -Check upstairs.
转过身去 转身
Turn around. turn around.
举手 放到脑后
Put your hands up. Behind your neck.
放好了
Keep them there.
什么都没有 安全
No, nothing here. All clear.
安全
All clear.
我现在就可以告诉你们 你们什么都找不到
You won't find a goddamn thing! I can tell you that right now.
你们屁都查不出来
Ain't got shit on me. Ain't got shit on me.
靠 我说了你们查不到的 什么都查不到!
Fuck! You ain't got nothing. I'm telling you. Nothing!
起来 傻鸟
Move, shitbird.
FBl 举起手来
FBl, show me your hands!
趴下 混蛋 趴下
Get down, fuck! Get down!
趴下
get down.
漂亮
Nice.
找到了
Bingo.
- 就在你们洗衣机后面 - 是海洛因 三百颗
-From behind your clothes washer. -That's heroin, 300 gelcaps.
今天中午的Chip Franklin(电台脱口秀节目主持人)脱口秀...
And on today's Chip Franklin Show at noon...
Chip会现场提问 Arundel Mills购物中心的业主
Chip will be live at Arundel Mills Mall asking local retailers:
"你们能把什么卖给拥有一切的人"
"What do you get for the guy who has everything?"
现在是Steve Stewart为您带来体育新闻 金莺队(美职棒球队)继续....
Now here's Steve Stewart with sports. The Orioles continue to....
火线重案组 第二季 第十一集 噩梦连连
The Wire S02E11 Bad Dreams
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"我要清白"  ---Sobotka
码头工人被拘 涉嫌双重谋杀
- 现在就把他抓了吧 - 还不够高调
-We could take him now. -Not enough profile.
该死的联邦探员
Fucking feds.
报告 27号目标正在移动
Be advised, target 27 is on the move.
我不明白 干嘛不抓Vondopoulos
I don't get it. Why leave Vondopoulos out on the street?
让他销毁证据的短信来自他上层
The text message that told him to clean up, it came from someone higher up.
我们尚不知道是谁
Someone we don't know.
我们搜查之后却放过他...
We leave him on the street after these raids...
他就可能联系上头的人
he'll probably make contact with whoever's above him.
要么短信 要么见面
Either another text message or a meet.
George Glekas怎么样了
What's with George Glekas?
恐怕是抓不了他了
I'm afraid he's gonna duck this warrant.
- Chester Karol Sobotka? - Frank Sobotka的儿子
-Chester Karol Sobotka? -It's Frank Sobotka's kid.
Frank的儿子杀了我们一个目标? 搞什么飞机
Frank's kid kills one of our targets? Are you shitting me?
为什么
Why? What for?
我们今早突击了他的店
We hit the store this morning.
连张纸片都没留下 只有地上的一摊血迹
Every shred of paper's gone. Just a bloodstain on the floor.
我们半小时后拿着逮捕令到他家...
So we go over to his house a half hour later with the warrant...
一群哭红眼的希腊亲戚盯着我们 当我们是活死人似的
and it's full up with red-eyed Greek relations looking at us like we're braindeads.
凶杀科 我是Shea
Homicide, Shea.
- 我是Daniels 东南区 - 有事吗 长官
-This is Daniels, out at Southeast. -Yes, sir.
前晚的Highlandtown凶杀案是谁管的
Who caught the Highlandtown murder the night before last?
Jay Landsman 长官
Jay Landsman, sir.
Landsman? 我马上过去
Landsman. I'll be right over.
去审讯室审犯人
Go get the interviews started.
死亡
- 警督? - 嘿 警督
-Lieutenant? -Hey, Lt.
他妈的什么情况
What the fuck is that about?
早上收获如何
How did we do this morning?
抓了Eton和Sergei 还有那个老太婆
Eton and Sergei are in. So is the madam.
Glekas就不知道了
Glekas, I'm not sure.
- 联邦探员正等着抓Sobotka - 他们还等什么
-The feds are waiting on Sobotka. -What are they waiting for?
你不会想知道的
You don't wanna know.
上帝 Larry...
Jesus, Larry....
现在情况是 如果工会的人 收拾不了这烂摊子...
The thing is, I think we gotta reach out to a criminal lawyer real quick.
我们得尽快找个刑事律师 他明天就要参加保释听证会了
If the union guys can't handle this mess... he's gonna have a bail hearing tomorrow.
- 你还知道什么细节吗 - 我一无所知...
-Do you have any details? -I don't know nothing...
只知道他被捕了 十点过后才能见他
except he's locked up for it. I can't see him till 10:00.
- 只有那时才行? - 对 探访时间
-That's the only time? -Visiting hours, yeah.
听着 会没事的
Look, everything's gonna be fine.
- FBl 都站好了 - 搞什么鬼
-FBl! All of you move, now! -What the fuck is this?
- FBl 站好 - 面墙站好
-FBl, move! -Against the wall.
他在这 他在这
He's here. he's here.
一波未平一波又起 Larry
Got another problem here, Larry.
码头的大人物
Big man on the docks.
现在没那么大牌了吧
You don't look so big now, do you?
妈
Ma.
爸
Pop.
pop.
没了
It's gone.
钱也没了
And the money, too.
他们说你得去警局一趟
They say you need to come in.
逮捕令在东南区警局放着
They said the warrant is at Southeastern police district.
他们来了
They're out there now.
表演时间到了 Franky
Showtime, Franky.
- Frank - 先生 说点什么
-Frank. -Sir, any comment?
是因你个人 还是整个工会?
Is it just you, or is it the whole union?
对你的指控你有什么要说的
What's your comment on the charges being brought against you?
先生 你对此有何看法 作何评论
Sir, do you have anything at all to say? Any comment at all?
你如何应对对你的指控
How will you answer the charges against you?
我问你 我查那些女尸案为的是谁
Let me ask you, who exactly am I working all these dead girls for?
凶杀科 对吗
The Homicide unit, right?
这个不会用用脑子给我打个电话...
The same Homicide unit that can't put two and two together and pick up a phone...
害我得从一天半后的巴尔的摩太阳报 得知消息的凶杀科
Ieaving me to read it a day-and-a-half later in The Baltimore Sun.
- 你们在犯罪现场采集了什么 - 照片 指纹 弹壳
-What did you take from the scene? -Photos, latents, spent casings.
操
Fuck.
他们把其他东西都处理掉了?
They cleaned everything else?
就算在这么个极度傻逼的警局里 你这行动也算傻到家了
Even for a supremely fucked-up police department this takes the prize.
那小鬼怎么样了
How'd the kid play it?
他签了份完整供状
He signed a full statement.
他说因为一两辆赃车起了争执
He said that there was an argument about a stolen car or two.
你觉得他愿意开口招出更多东西吗
Think he'll open up and talk more?
他已经被起诉和收监
He's been processed and assigned a PD.
如果你想在那小鬼身上碰碰运气 得先搞定他的律师
If you want to take a run at the kid, you're gonna have to get around his lawyer.
抱歉 警督 我的错
I'm sorry, Lieutenant. It's my bad.
说名字 混蛋 你叫什么名字
State your name, asshole. What's your name?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
说名字
State your name.
拜托 你清楚怎么回事 告诉我们你的名字
Come on, you know this part. Give us a name.
你们要的名字
There is your name.
说你的名字
State your name.
名字都没有?
No name?
- 那我们从现在开始就叫你Boris吧 - Boris
-For now, we'll just call you Boris. -Boris.
怎么老是"Boris"?
Why always "Boris"?
诈骗 电汇欺诈 走私海洛因
Racketeering. Wire fraud. Conspiracy to import heroin.
违反联邦海关条例
Conspiracy to violate federal customs statutes.
逼良为娼
White slavery.
我们今天只起诉违反海关条例 Sobotka先生
Today we're only charging the customs violations, Mr. Sobotka.
不过最终大陪审团的起诉 会包括更多罪名
But eventually, a grand jury indictment will expose you to a lot more.
告诉我们些名字 坦白从宽 既能帮你 也能帮整个工会
Name names, and come clean. You help yourself and your union.
帮我的工会?
Help my union?
25年来 我们都在慢慢走向灭亡
For 25 years, we've been dying slow down there.
船坞在生锈 码头空荡荡的
Dry docks rusting, piers standing empty.
我的朋友和他们的孩子 人人像得了癌症
My friends and their kids, like we got the cancer.
没人给我们哪怕一根救命稻草
No lifeline got thrown all that time. Nothing from nobody.
你们却说想帮我们?
And now you wanna help us?
帮我?
Help me?
- 你全名是什么? - Michael McArdle
-What's your full name? -Michael McArdle.
- "麦克白" - 对 没错
-White Mike. -Yeah, that's right.
听好了 Mikey
Listen to this, Mikey.
我得确定那晚不是你们的人 把那具尸体扔到Potee街
I wanna know it wasn't your people dropped that body on Potee Street the other night.
我问是因为那尸体有个希腊名字...
I'm asking 'cause it was someone with a Greek-ass name...
只要不是扔在我房子前面 才不关我鸟事
and fuck if he wasn't dumped in front of a house I was using.
他有手吗 他有脸吗
Did he have hands? Did he have a face?
有吗 那就与我们无关
Yes? Then it wasn't us.
我们突袭了你的供货商
We hit your suppliers.
他们自己收拾干净 却留你背黑锅
They cleaned up and left you holding the dirt.
- 什么供货商? - 你在这录音里谈论毒品交易
-Suppliers of what? -You discussed a drug buy on this tape.
我们有你在藏毒点和...
We also have photographs tying you to your stash house...
希腊人的Newkirk街货仓进货的照片
and putting you at The Greek's warehouse over on Newkirk Street for re-ups.
帮自己个忙 Mike
Do yourself a solid here, Mike.
- 有什么计划 - 这只是个拘留听审 Frank
-What's the plan? -This is just a detention hearing, Frank.
你没有潜逃风险 也没有前科
You're not a flight risk, you have no meaningful priors.
而且目前为止他们只对你进行一项起诉
And so far they've only hit you with one count.
地方法官会问我们些基本问题
The magistrate's gonna ask us some basic questions.
除非异常情况 你一小时内就能离开
Barring anything unforeseen, you're out in an hour.
- 我什么也没说 - 那最好了
-I said nothing to them suits. -All the better.
- 这个Eton 他负责什么 - 毒品
-This Eton, he's in charge of what exactly? -The dope.
他是哪里人 希腊的?
He's what, Greek?
犹太人 你知道来自犹太国家
He's a Jew. You know, from that Jew country they got.
- 那这个叫Sergei的人呢 - Sergei是打手
-And what about the guy they call Sergei? -Sergei's straight muscle.
- 听着 我要吃东西 - 好吧 你想吃什么
-Look, I need something to eat. -Okay, what do you want?
两条热狗 一杯草莓苏打
Two hot dogs and a strawberry soda.
我总会买错东西
I'd fuck the order up.
一定得是草莓的?
It's gotta be strawberry?
哥就好这口
Hook a brother up.
大个子 别跟Omar来这套
Big man, that ain't gonna work for Omar.
没关系
It's all right.
多久了 一年了?
Been what, a year?
小子 你不知道 我一直盼着再见你一面
Boy, you don't know, I been dreaming of running into you again.
你有心 我从命
You got a focus. I give you that.
人有目标才会那样 懂我的意思吗
Man be like that when he got work to do. You know what I mean?
你做得够绝了 Bird入狱
I think you've done enough. Bird gone.
Wee-Bey担了所有的谋杀罪 大概一辈子也出不来了
Wee-Bey copped out to all them murders. He in jail now forever and a day.
Stinkum? 你亲手结果了他
Stinkum? I mean, you closed the book on that nigger your damn self.
Avon 眼下赔钱做买卖
Avon, he out of pocket for the time being.
就剩你了
Leaving you.
- 你想做个了断吗 - 搞清楚 伙计 没什么了断
-You looking for closure? -Lookit, man, ain't no closure.
除非Brandon现在就还魂出现在这
Not unless Brandon walk up out his grave and come up in this room right now.
我只知道血债血偿
See, all I know is whoever did him that way, they gets got.
犯下血债的还毫发无损呢
Whoever did him that way, they still out there right now.
你是要假装这事跟你无关吗
So now you gonna play like you had nothing to do with it.
不 我不骗你
No, I can't lie.
我对你们下了格杀令 但是你们先到我藏毒点捣蛋的
I put the motherfucking paper out on y'all. But y'all was fucking with my stash.
这之后 大家都按江湖规矩办了
Anything after that, part of the game.
也许吧 但Brandon的事我不会这么算了
Maybe. But see, I went past that with Brandon.
那不是我 也不是Avon干的
That wasn't me. That wasn't Avon, either.
Bird和其他几个人旁观了 但动手的另有其人
Bird and them were there to see it. But another man did all the extras:
用烟头烫...
all that cigarette shit...
挖眼睛
all that bullshit with the eyes.
这人要给自己立威...
See now, this man, he building a rep for himself...
他急需对付你
and he wants you bad.
那些残忍的酷刑是他的名片
The brutal shit, that's his calling card.
带着个小蝴蝶结的混球 打哪来的...
Little bow-tie wearing motherfucker from out of....
纽约?
NYC?
对 小人一个
Yeah, small dude.
他什么来头
What he go by?
Mouzone大兄
Brother Mouzone.
我知道你听说过他 对吗
I know you heard of him, right?
如果你们想对付他...
So if y'all got the mind to go after him...
我可能给你们指条路
I might be able to point you in that direction.
为什么
Why?
你小弟的事是生意场的事
What happened to your boy was business.
但他受的罪 你有权耿耿于怀
But how that shit happened, you got the right to take that to heart.
我想到了让我们扯平的办法
I figure that'll make us even.
你想知道那黑鬼现在在哪吗
Now, you wanna know where this nigger is?
- 我们得坐下来好好谈谈 Frank - 我得去见我儿子
-We need to sit down and talk, Frank. -I gotta see my son.
他说的没错 我们去喝杯咖啡吧
The man's right. Let's grab a cup of coffee or something.
现在不行 我要清白
Not now, I need to get clean.
Sergei他们...
Sergei and them...
干掉了Mau Mau Willis
they did Mau Mau Willis.
- 他们为什么要对付他 - 他失信于犹太人
-Why'd they chill him? -He was welshing on the Jew.
Sergei是个打手 但他和Eton遵某人的命令行事
Okay, Sergei's a soldier. But he and Eton report to somebody.
- 谁是他们的上级 Mike? - 不知道
-Who's above those two, Mike? -I don't know.
- 你不知道? - 也不想知道
-You don't know? -Never did wanna know.
上帝 Zig 警察干的?
God in heaven, Zig, the cops do that to you?
不是
Ain't the cops.
律师说很难保释
Lawyers are saying the bail might be tough.
我在想办法
I'm trying.
你知道我在想办法 对吧
You know I'm trying, right?
- 怎么回事 - 不知道
-What happened? -I don't know.
我厌倦了
I got tired.
我厌倦了被人当笑话
I got tired of being the punchline to every joke.
你有问题可以跟我说啊
You had problems, you could've come to me.
你该跟我说的
You could've said something.
你不会听的
You wouldn't have heard.
你整天忙于争取疏通运河
You were always too busy dredging up the canal.
确保合适的人当选
Making sure the right bum got elected.
请酒吧里的人再喝一轮
Buying another round for the house.
我曾经还以为你都把时间花在工作上呢
I always used to think you were working all them hours you spent away.
那是为了工作 Zig 即便不是为了工作
It was all work, Zig, even when it wasn't.
也是为了你 为了你母亲
For you, for your mother.
我打赌你还没告诉她我在这
I bet you didn't even tell her I was in here, did you?
又或者是你说了...
Maybe you did...
而她却喝了三片戊巴比妥钠(镇静剂)睡过去了
and she already took three Nembutals, sleeping the day away.
- 别把她扯进来 - 没想把她扯进来 别担心
-Leave her out of this. -She's out of it, don't worry.
爸...
Pop...
一想到我对店里那孩子的所作所为...
when I seen what I did to that kid down at the store...
我就恶心得想吐
it made me sick to my stomach.
- 那不怪你 Zig - 不怪我?
-That ain't you, Zig. -It ain't?
因为我们流的不是相同的血 爸
Because the same blood don't flow for us, Pop.
我是说 我希望是 可不是
I mean, I wish it did, but it don't.
你比自己想的要像我
You're more like me than you know.
你是Sobotka家的人
You're a Sobotka.
我是个傻帽
Fucked is what I am.
我还能说什么
What the fuck can I say?
最大的突破口是"麦克白" McArdle
Best progress so far is "White Mike" McArdle.
他已经站在了悬崖边上 我们今天就让Pearlman过来
He's standing on the edge of the cliff. We're gonna get Pearlman in today
看看她能不能让他出来作证
to see what she can do to step him off.
还有 我们仍在追捕Sobotka的侄子
Also, we're still hunting the Sobotka nephew.
Herc和Carver负责
Herc and Carver are on that.
但即便这些毒贩转作证人...
Still, my guess is the drug players...
供出Eton和Sergei
even if they roll, give us Eton and Sergei.
但我们仍然对付不了这个...
The case gets thin when we get up to this...
Spiros Vondopoulos
Spiros Vondopoulos.
这些希腊人 名字真别拗
Boy, them Greeks and those twisted-ass names.
少说两句希腊人吧 人家孕育了现代文明
Lay off the Greeks. They invented civilization.
是吗 照样不咋地
Yeah? Ass-fucking, too.
我们对Vondopoulos都知道些什么
What exactly do we know about Vondopoulos?
我们得盯紧了 搞清楚他究竟是谁
We should stay on him, see who he really is.
这样如何
How about it?
给我们点你那儿装备精良的监视小队?
Throw us a few of your well-equipped surveillance teams?
你该注意到了 警督 这屋里的联邦探员就剩我了
In case you haven't noticed, Lieutenant, I'm the only fed still in the room.
联邦检察官已经找到了对付工会的证据
The US attorney has what he wants with the union guys...
也就是说 对我们来说这基本上算结案了
which means my field office is pretty much over this case.
好吧 我们自己查Vondopoulos
Okay, we're on Vondopoulos ourselves.
我为他感到遗憾...
I'm sorry for him...
也为你遗憾
and for you.
我们该多关心关心家人
We should've paid more attention to our own.
说得好像我能阻止Ziggy干出那种事一样
Like I could've stopped Ziggy from what he'd done.
说得好像还有谁能管得住他
Like anyone could ever control him.
我也是在说我的孩子
I was thinking of my boy, too.
他们是想一网成擒
They're dropping the net on all the guys.
只要以后集装箱里的东西 不神秘消失 他会没事的
Ain't no secret things get lost in them cans now and again. He'll be all right.
他们把我房子翻了个底朝天 Frank
They tossed my house, Frank.
他们可不会为丢了几瓶伏特加这么干
They don't do that when there's a couple of cases of vodka missing.
他们让我签这张搜查令 算是给他们找到的东西打的收条
They made me sign the search warrant. That's a receipt-like for what they found.
海洛因 Frank 从这儿搜出来的
Heroin, Frank. From this house.
不 不可能 绝不可能
No, that ain't right. That can't be right.
我知道Nicky和Zig偷东西 照相机之类的 但不是这些
I knew Nicky and Zig was boosting stuff. Cameras, shit like that. Nothing like this.
你知道?
You knew?
而一旦Nicky偷上瘾了 见钱眼开...
And once Nicky got used to boosting stuff and seeing a little money...
你觉得他会怎么做 突然之间改邪归正 洗手不干?
what did you think he was gonna do? Turn straight all of a sudden and give it up?
不 Frank
No, Frank.
一旦他尝到甜头...
Once you gave him a taste on the house, just....
不会... 我是说 他知道的
That was never.... I mean, he knew. He knew.
我的所作所为 放行那些集装箱而拿的钱 都是为了维持现有的一切
Everything I did, the cans I let through the money we got from that went to keeping what we had.
去你的 Frank
God damn it, Frank!
别为这事找什么烂借口
Don't let that excuse this. Not this.
Frank叔叔 有担待
Uncle Frank, with the big shoulders.
"如果事情搞砸了 交给我叔叔"
"If it's broke, give it to my uncle.
"他能弥补"
"He can fix it."
嘿 小凶手 我有东西给你 过来
Hey, Killer. I got something for you, come here.
你买了最新一期的Harper's?
You got the new Harper's yet?
你知道这条街的商店...
Now, you know stores down the way...
除了Vibe和Handguns(二者皆为杂志)就没别的了
don't have nothing past Vibe and Handguns Today.
你要的话还有些色情杂志
Some titty mags, too, if you need.
好吧 了解
All right. I got you.
随时为您服务 好吧?
I'm gonna hook you up, though, all right?
嘿 小鬼 我说了要给你点好东西
Hey, boy. Told you I had something for you.
给你
There you go.
乖孩子
That's my good boy.
卸船的好日子
Good day for a ship.
这里是工会职业介绍所 Frank 只接待干活的装卸工
This is the hiring hall, Frank. Working stevedores only.
Big Roy 你的卡让我用用
Big Roy, let me have your card.
你想用我的卡干什么
What do you want my card for?
不是说你 小Big Roy 我要用你的卡
Not you. Little Big Roy, let me hold your card.
我还要留着用呢 我今天给圣乔治海角号干活
I need it. I'm gonna work the Cape St. George today.
- 我帮你干 - 帮我干?
-I'll work it for you. -Work it for me?
我用你的卡上船干活 你去Clement街的酒吧喝一杯
I work the ship on your card. You work a barstool down Clement Street.
这周末拿工资
End of the week, you get paid.
嘿 Phil
Hey, Phil.
我要上圣乔治海角号
I'm putting up for the Cape St. George.
看着跟照片不像啊
I don't see no resemblance.
我们都是秃头波兰人 你他妈还想知道什么
We're both bald, we're both Polacks. What the fuck else you need to know?
谁也帮我干干活啊
Who's gonna work for me?
- 那小子一天一个样啊 - Perry Ellis(名牌)还是什么
-A different look for our boy. -Perry Ellis or something.
你这种一副邋遢样的混球...
How would a just-rolled-out-of-bed-looking motherfucker like you...
懂什么时尚
know the designer?
好吧 我猜的
Okay, I'm guessing.
那是Joseph Abboud
It's a Joseph Abboud.
他用黑纽扣代替运动夹克的黄铜色纽扣
He puts dark buttons instead of brass on his blazers.
那是Abboud的风格
That's the Abboud signature.
你知道太关注自己衣着的人 都被人叫什么吧
You know what they call a guy who pays that much attention to his clothes, right?
成年人
A grown-up.
跟上
We're up.
- 12-14 出发了 - 收到 11-34
-12-14, let's go. -Copy, 1 1-34.
- 还是第一次 - 检查员出汗
-That's a first. -Sweat from a checker.
- 搞定没? - 行了
-You all right? -Ready.
也许你该在人行道上架个画架...
Maybe you ought to set up an easel on the sidewalk...
- 然后画个素描 - 就搞定了
-and do a sketch instead. -I'm fine.
- 有什么忠告 - 嗯 利用这城市
-Anything I ought to know? -Yeah. Use the city.
窗户 镜子 后视镜之类能反光的东西
Windows, mirrors, reflections, anything like that.
保持通话频道 听见没
Stay on my frequency, hear?
Vondopoulos会徒步走出停车场...
Vondopoulos should be coming out of the garage on foot...
- 马上就要出来了 - 收到
-right about now. -Copy that.
Beadie Russell 你知道 她刚开始没那么牛
Beadie Russell. She wasn't much when we started, you know.
但现在开窍了
But now she's got game.
谢谢
Thank you.
12-14 目标进入五楼一个房间
1 2-14. I got him going into a fifth floor room.
记下房号 下楼到大堂
Note the number then get down to the lobby.
- 在那等他 - 收到
-Wait on him there. -Copy.
她跟踪Vondopoulos走进一间房间 可能要等一段时间
She's got Vondopoulos in a room. It could be a while.
收到
Copy.
- 这些东西都要装车? - 他们是这么跟我说的
-All this shit's going out to chassis? -That's what they tell me.
我们需要台堆高机 这里都快搞定了
We need a forklift. We're almost done here.
12-14 Vondopoulos 和一个中年蓝衣人...
12-14. Vondopoulos and another man, middle-aged, blue suit...
出了酒店前门 就在我后面 收到吗
Ieaving the front door of the hotel. They'rejust behind me. Copy?
收到
Copy.
11-34
11-34.
目标及同伴 蓝衣服 随时离开酒店
Subject and companion, blue suit, leaving the hotel any moment now.
收到 我们会盯着
Copy, we got the eyeball.
那个跟Vondopoulos一起的一定是条大鱼
The man with Vondopoulos has got to be big.
- 看看那昂贵的衣服 - 对 还有纽扣什么的
-I mean, look at that expensive suit. -Yeah, with them buttons and all.
- 奔驰就丢在这了? - 会有麻烦 是偷来的
- We leave the Benz here? - (speaking greek)It's hot.
他们没回奔驰上 你们看到他们没有
They didn't come back to the Benz. You got them down there?
没看到
Negative.
- 你快做完了? - 还有这9个要卸
-You about done? -These nine here still got to be stripped.
- 看着容易做起来难 - 什么不是呢
-Harder than it looks. -What ain't?
- 你听过"登月男"是怎么得名的吗 - 听过 但关我鸟事
-You hear how Moonshot got his name? -Yeah, and I could give a fuck.
那间房是谁登记的
Who was the room registered to?
Stephen Rados 登记的地址是特区西北
Stephen Rados. He gave a Northwest D.C. address.
也许是跟那个西装革履的人 也许不是
Maybe that's the man with the good tailor. Maybe not.
我们得全力追查这家伙 看看有什么收获
We should run out the paper trail on this guy, see what we turn up.
作为我们这次突击的唯一战利品...
As to our only tangible piece of progress from the raids...
我们能拿"麦克白"做什么文章
what can we do for our friend White Mike?
他招出供货商 能获得长期缓刑
He rolls on his suppliers, and he can walk with a long probation.
- 如果他需要我们还能给他挪个地 - 证人保护?
-And we can move him, if he needs. -Witness protection?
既然和FBI合作 此时不用 更待何时?
Why have the feds with you if they're not gonna step up every now and then?
等等 你能给一个毒贩这么多好处?
Wait a second. You're gonna give a drug dealer a ride like that?
那Frank Sobotka呢
What about Frank Sobotka?
联邦探员侦讯了他 但一无所获
The feds took a shot at him and got nothing.
至少他们这么跟我说的
Or so they tell me.
就我理解 他们更关心肢解工会...
The way I read it, they cared more about busting up the union--
而不是别的什么 如果我们直接找Frank呢
Than anything else in the case. If we came at Frank straight?
你无权跟他进行任何司法交易
You can't make him any kind of specific offer yourself.
只有我可以 那也是要经过总部同意
Only I can do that, and only after I get an okay from my front office.
- 她可以埋下一颗种子 - 找不到更好的信使了 律师
-She could plant the seed. -There's no better messenger, Counselor.
试试吧
Take a shot.
- 你去他家? - 工会大厅 那才是他家
-You going to his house? -The Union Hall. That's his house.
多谢等候 Brucie 抱歉我来晚了
Thanks for waiting, Brucie. Sorry I'm late.
这节骨眼上我就不该跟你见面
I shouldn't even be seen with you at this point.
我只想趁还可以时 把我们的事交代清楚
I just wanna settle our business while we still can.
显然我这动作不是要掏出更多钱来
It ain't like I'm gonna get my hands on more cash, obviously.
粮食码头计划玩完了
The grain pier is dead.
半数我们争取到的票都变卦了
Half the votes we had lined up are walking sideways now.
他们看了报纸 Frank
They read the paper, Frank.
那又怎样 我有罪?
So what? So I'm dirty.
粮食码头归粮食码头 对吧
The grain pier's still the grain pier, right?
他们又不是给我投票 Brucie 这不是我个人的事
They ain't voting for me, Brucie! It ain't about me!
我不想骗你 Frank
I'm not gonna lie. frank
现在FBI在查你 没人会跟你站同一边
No one is gonna stand with us now that the FBI is on you.
- 他们被吓到了 - 被什么吓到
-They're scared. -Of what?
他们拿了钱 Frank
They took the money, Frank.
如果他们投了赞成票 他们会觉得联邦探员也会查他们
And now if they deliver the votes, they figure the feds will be on them, too.
抱歉 Frank
I'm sorry, Frank.
如果你能让这事过去...
You find a way of putting this FBI thing to bed...
也许我们下次会期能让 粮食码头卷土重来 好吗
maybe we can come back the next session with the grain pier. all right?
有些人知道自己欠了你这几票
You'll have a couple of people down there knowing they owe you a vote or two.
我不知道还能说什么 抱歉 Frank
I don't know what else to say. I don't. I'm sorry, Frank.
你知道问题出在哪吗 Brucie?
You know what the trouble is, Brucie?
我们曾在这个国家自力更生
We used to make shit in this country. Build shit.
现在却要把手伸进别人的口袋里
Now we just put our hand in the next guy's pocket.
你不能只吃橄榄 点些东西吧 小羊羔肉什么的
Come on, you can't eat only olives. Order something. Lamb or something.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
这么多烦心事呢
All this trouble.
- 我们的伙伴都可靠吗 - 是的
-So, our associates, they are strong? -Yes.
我不担心我们的人 可以试试在庭审前把他们弄出来
I don't worry about our people. We can try to get them out before the trial.
就算不行 他们也不会背叛我们
If not, they will stand for us.
他们知道的太多了 不能再添麻烦了
We have shown them too much. There will be no more trouble.
这点一定要确保
We must make certain of this.
- 也许还有别的办法 - 只有一个方法能保证
-Maybe there's another way. -There is only one sure way.
听我说 如果我能保证 Frank Sobotka叔侄...
Hear me out. If I could guarantee that Frank Sobotka and his nephew...
会保持沉默...
would be silent...
你不希望这么做吗
wouldn't you prefer that?
但你保证不了
But you cannot guarantee this.
Frank的儿子 那个在George的店里 枪杀他的傻帽...
Frank's son, the idiot who shot George in his store...
他会在监狱里待很久...
he is going to jail for a long time...
除非...
unless....
店里有个受伤的年轻职员
There was a young clerk wounded that day in the store.
公诉人想让他出庭作证
The prosecutors want to use him as a witness.
我认识他家人
I know his family.
Frank Sobotka的孩子会没事的
Frank Sobotka will have his son back.
如果能替他做到这点 他还会跟警察说什么呢
If a man can have this, why would he talk to the police?
那Frank的侄子呢
What about Frank's nephew?
他是那傻帽的表兄 他想要的跟Frank一样
He is the idiot's cousin. He wants the same thing as Frank.
不管怎么说 我不担心Niko
Anyway, I don't worry about Niko.
你挺欣赏他的 Spiros
You are fond of him, Spiros.
你该生个孩子了
You should've had a son.
那接着我就该找个老婆了
But then I would've had a wife.
如果那条蛆虫到午夜还不现身 这笔账我就要记下了
If this maggot doesn't post by midnight, I'm gonna take it personal.
那傻鸟住在他父母家地下室里
The shitbird lives in his parents' basement.
这样的家伙还能跑哪去
Where's a guy like that gonna run?
你想跟Tasha阿姨一起? 来啊
You wanna go with Auntie Tasha? Come on.
轻点 松开吧 宝贝
Nice and easy, honey. come on.
- 过来 - 好了 走吧 宝贝
-Come here. -All right, come on, baby.
怎么样了 大个子? 派对在哪呢
What's up, big man? Where the party at?
这里没什么派对 小姐
Ain't no party up in here, girl.
我们还以为Darnell和大家都吸上了呢
We thought Darnell and everybody was gonna get their smoke on.
你不认识Darnell?
Don't you know Darnell?
这乖孩子叫什么名字
What's this good boy's name?
嘿 孩子
Hey, boy.
今天过得怎么样 还好吗 好孩子
How you doing today? You been good? This a good boy.
- 搞定 - 车会发动着
-There it is. -Car will be running.
什么事 Lamar?
What is it, Lamar?
赶快了结吧
No need to prolong this.
不 我们有得是时间
No, we got time.
- 你杀了我手下? - 不 他睡得正香呢
-You kill my man? -No, he's resting.
- 我说 你就不想知道为什么? - 不怎么想
-I'm saying, ain't you wanna know? -Not particularly.
约一年前 一个叫Brandon的孩子 来到Baltimore
About a year ago, a boy name Brandon got got here in Baltimore.
死前被棒打 被烧
Stuck and burned before he passed.
- 游戏就是游戏 - 没错
-The game is the game. -Indeed.
那孩子长得不赖
See, that boy was beautiful.
你们实在不必把他弄成那样
Wasn't no need for y'all to do him the way y'all did.
听明白了吗
You feel me?
- 你说一年前? - 差不多吧
-A year, you say? -About that.
你的情报有误
You've got some wrong information.
伙计 你是骗我好活命
Man, you lying to live.
我听从上帝的安排
I'm at peace with my God.
你要动手就动手
Do what you will.
这么说你知道?
So you know?
发生在你小弟身上的事 不是我的风格
What happened to your boy, it's not my style.
看你背部流血的样子 子弹像是穿过去了
The way you bleeding out your back, looks like that bullet bore clean through.
近距离用9毫米子弹是这种效果
9 mm at close range will do that.
这是紧急电话 你要叫警察还是救护车?
Emergency. Do you need police or ambulance?
我要报告一起新汽车旅馆的枪击事件
I wanna report a shooting over here at the new motel.
- 北大街那个 221号房 - 先生?
-On North Avenue. Room 221 . -Sir?
我的朋友 Beatrice
My pal, Beatrice.
怎么 你又想抓我? 难道不是 有个一罪不两罚什么的说法吗
What, you gonna run me in again? lsn't that like double jeopardy or some shit?
别来这套 别这样
Stop it, just stop it.
- 跟我谈谈 - 谈什么
-Talk to me. -And say what?
我自己还想坐在这弄清楚呢
I'm sitting here trying to figure it out myself.
冰冻三尺非一日之寒
It didn't happen overnight.
我知道我做错了
I knew I was wrong.
但我认为我是为正确的理由做错事 懂吗
But in my head, I thought I was wrong for the right reasons, you know?
错也分不同种
There are different kinds of wrong.
你来这干嘛 Bea?
What're you doing here, Bea?
我想你过去 不戴手铐
I'd like you to come in. Not in cuffs.
因为是你想去
Because you want to.
我在给你指条明路 Frank
I'm opening a door here, Frank.
我没法承诺什么
I can't promise you anything.
但你来吧 我们可以从这里开始
Just come in. We'll start from there.
你比那些跟你狼狈为奸的人好多了
You're better than them you got in bed with.
- 我们的Vondopoulos没回家? - 也许走运了
-Our man Vondopoulos didn't come home? -Maybe he got lucky.
也许我们倒霉了
Maybe we didn't.
你认为他发现了盯梢者 所以丢下了奔驰车?
You think he ditched the Benz because he picked up the tail?
码头的Nicky
Nicky from the docks.
如果你昨晚不打电话 我根本找不到你
If you hadn't called last night, I'd have never found you.
放松 Niko 拜托
Relax, Niko, come on.
就像我在电话里跟你说的
It's like I told you on the phone.
会没事的 我们能摆平这事
It is going to be all right. We can make it all right.
我就不该上你们的贼船
I should have never gone down the road with you people.
拜托 你只想做点成绩出来
Come on. You tried to make something of yourself.
这没什么坏处 况且你还有朋友呢
There's no harm in that. And you still have friends.
我被追捕了
I'm busted.
还有我叔叔和整个工会 还有Ziggy?
So is my uncle and the whole fucking union. And Ziggy?
- 上帝 - 我们待他也如朋友
-Christ! -We will be a friend to him, too.
你们什么也做不了 Ziggy玩完了
Nothing your people can do about that. Ziggy's done.
没什么玩完了 Niko 没有
Nothing is done, Niko. Nothing.
看看
Take a look.
那不是你名字
That's not your name.
很多名字 很多护照
Many names, many passports.
我们能做的多着呢
We can do many things.
你们能为Ziggy做什么?
What can you do for Ziggy?
我们要的仅仅是忠诚
We ask only loyalty.
他们干嘛要用棍子 用脚踢不就好了吗
Why do they need sticks? Can't they kick it with their feet?
她让我坦诚地过来 我就来了
She asked me straight-up to come in, so I'm here.
首先 我们得知道你想要什么
First, we need to know what you're looking for.
我们不希望之后有所误会
We don't want any misunderstandings later on.
我只是想帮帮我儿子
I'm just looking for, you know, some help with my son.
- 他不能关在现在这地方 - 我们会把他移送到郡里
-He can't jail where they got him. -We move him to a county facility.
- 我的侄子呢 - 他被逮捕并起诉
-What about my nephew? -He gets arrested and charged.
但鉴于他和你与我们合作...
But for his cooperation and yours...
缓刑过后 原罪刑宣告继续有效 和原判刑失效相对
我们可以给他一般缓刑
we can live with straight probation.
但我们能为你家人做什么...
But what we can and cannot do for you and your family...
- 都取决于你的合作程度 - 你是说 我提供多少消息?
-depends on the level of your cooperation. -You mean, how much I give you?
他们干的坏事我都知道
I got dirt on all of them.
我自己的也全招了 你么想知道什么都行 除了工会其他的我都说
I'll put myself in, too. Whatever you need. Anything but the union.
我不会把工会的人扯进来 我会告诉你们集装箱女尸的情况
I ain't putting in no union men. I'll give you them dead girls in the can.
供出希腊人 他们那帮兔崽子...
I'll give you The Greek, all them sons of bitches...
什么我都坦白 只要关照我儿子和侄儿
just to have it off my chest. Just look to my son and my nephew.
Sobotka先生 我得建议你...
Mr. Sobotka, at this point I have to advise you...
你需要一个律师
you need to retain the services of an attorney.
不是现在就全说了?
We're not gonna do this now?
你需要有律师在场
You need to have a lawyer present in the room.
你明天找个律师来 我们就能开始了
You have that, we can make this happen first thing tomorrow.
Sobotka先生 我想问问
Mr. Sobotka, I gotta ask.
为什么你不用你的手机了
Why did you stop using your cell phone?
你们给我做了标记 以为我不知道吗?
You guys flagged it. You think I didn't know?
桥下?
Under the bridge?
那里很开阔 警察应该没法窃听或干嘛
It's out in the open. I guess the cops can't bug it or nothing.
这些家伙 要做个大手笔的保护行动
These guys, they got a big operation to protect.
他们是跨国组织
They're global-like.
- 他们还真厉害啊 - 你想象不到他们能做什么
-They're really something? -You got no idea.
我想我很清楚他们是什么货色
I think I got a pretty clear picture of what they're about.
我们说的可不是一群 在码头偷橄榄油的贼
We ain't talking about a bunch of thieves rolling drums of olive oil off the docks.
海洛因?
Heroin?
这他妈的怎么回事 Nick? 看着我
How the fuck did that happen, Nick? Look at me!
你不过还是个孩子
You ain't much more than a kid.
我本该更清楚这点的 我让你跟他们掺和为的什么
Me, I should've known better. I put you up with them, for what?
我残害家人为的什么
I flushed my fucking family, for what?
你知道那是什么吗 Nicky? 知道吗
You know what that is, Nicky? Do you?
之前提到该地被地产开发商相中
共管公寓
A condominium.
我不去
I ain't going down there.
我要做的是去警察局自首
What I'm gonna do is, I'm gonna go in and talk with the police.
那才是正确的 那些贱种怎么对我 我就怎么对他们
That's right. I'm gonna do to those cocksuckers what they did to me.
- 你不能那么干 - 为什么
-You can't do that. -Why not?
他们能在Ziggy的事上帮我们
They wanna meet with us on Ziggy.
他们能搞定目击证人...
They can lean on that witness...
他开枪打那孩子时在场的那个人
that kid that he shot, the one that was there in the store.
他会作证"双G"当时拿着枪
The kid's gonna say that Double G had the gun.
会把他说成是自卫什么的
That it was like self-defense or some shit.
Ziggy会被释放的 Frank叔叔
Ziggy could walk, Uncle Frank.
他会没事的
He could.
- 为此他们有什么要求 - 忠诚
-And for that they want what? -Loyalty.
混球
Motherfuckers!
我会去跟他们谈谈
I'll hear them out.
- 好的 我载你过去 - 不 我一个人去
-All right, I'll drive. -No, it's just me.
你不能再跟这些家伙接触了
You ain't dealing with those guys no more.
- Frank叔叔 我和Spiros... - 我他妈的不想让你跟来 Nick
-Uncle Frank, me and Spiros-- -I don't fucking want you with me, Nick!
回家去
Go home!
建议与...
...Sobotka Frank会话...
发送
主题:建议与Sobotka Frank会话---此人为案件调查目标
Sobotka声称深谙被调查的犯罪组织 包括他指认的头目"希腊人"
其涉嫌集装箱女尸案  建议在Sobotka得到代表律师后开展对话
你的办法...
Your way...
行不通
it won't work.